(this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]=this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]||[]).push([[9],{163:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),o=a.n(n),r=a(7),s=[{question:"What is HackTJ?",answer:o.a.createElement("p",null,"HackTJ is a student-run hackathon where you will have 24 hours to learn how to code and/or work with your friends to make your idea come to life.")},{question:"When is HackTJ?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ will start on Saturday, April 24 and run until Sunday, April 25.")},{question:"Who can attend?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is open to any and all current high school students. If you're not a high school student but would like to attend, consider coming as a judge, mentor, or volunteer.")},{question:"Is there any cost?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Nope! Thanks to our sponsors, HackTJ is completely free!")},{question:"Is there a deadline?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Registration for participants, judges, mentors, and volunteers opens on September 25 at 8 p.m. Registration for participants closes on October 16\u2014this is a hard deadline; we do not accept submissions after 8 p.m. Judges, mentors, and volunteers will be able to register until the start of the event.")},{question:"Do you have a code of conduct?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Yes, good question! We have adopted the"," ",o.a.createElement(r.b,{to:"conduct.pdf",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"MLH code of conduct"),", which all attendees will be required to adhere to.")},{question:"Isn't hacking illegal?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,'In the context of a hackathon, "hacking" is to build a real application over the length of the event. It\'s important to not confuse this with illegal hacking, which is gaining unauthorized access to a computer.')},{question:"Do I need a team?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"If you already have a team of 2-4 people you want to work with, that's awesome! If not don't worry because we'll have an opportunity for people to join a team if they need one.")},{question:"What if I don't know how to code?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Come to HackTJ! Coding is fun, creative, and an important skill, and HackTJ is the perfect way to learn. We'll have workshops and mentors to help guide you.")},{question:"What prizes can I win?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ hosts prizes for the best projects in the following categories: Overall Hack, Web App, Mobile App,Design, Social Impact Hack, and Beginner Hack (first-year coder teams). Major League Hacking and some of our partners also host their own Sponsored Prizes, which you can explore when the 7.5 Devpost goes live.")},{question:"How do I register?",answer:o.a.createElement("ol",null,o.a.createElement("li",null,"At 8 p.m. on September 25, a button will appear at the top of this site. Click this."),o.a.createElement("li",null,"You will be redirected to a page where you can click the appropriate form."),o.a.createElement("li",null,"Fill out the questions. Near the end, there will be a few questions where you can upload your forms.",o.a.createElement("ul",null,o.a.createElement("li",null,"In order to speed up the registration process, print out these forms, fill them out, and scan them beforehand."))))},{question:"How are tickets decisions made?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Tickets decisisons are made based on a variety of factors, including the registration time. Sign up quickly to increase the chance that you are given a HackTJ 8.0 ticket!")}],l=a(6),i=(a(60),o.a.memo((function(e){var t=e.data,a=Object(n.useState)(-1),r=Object(l.a)(a,2),s=r[0],i=r[1];return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"wrapper"},t.map((function(e,t){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"container ".concat(s===t?"selected":"").concat(s-1===t?" round-bottom":""),key:t,onClick:function(){i(s===t?-1:t)}},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},e.question),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"content"},o.a.createElement("div",null,e.answer)))})))})));a(61),t.default=function(){return o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement("a",{className:"anchor",id:"faq",href:"#faq"},"FAQ"),o.a.createElement("section",{className:"green faq"},o.a.createElement("h1",{className:"section-title"},"FAQ"),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"faq-wrapper"},o.a.createElement(i,{data:s.slice(0,s.length/2)}),o.a.createElement(i,{data:s.slice(s.length/2)})),o.a.createElement("p",{className:"large bottom-question"},"If your question is not answered here, just ask us:"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hello@hacktj.org"),".")))}},60:function(e,t,a){},61:function(e,t,a){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=9.ceda8cd3.chunk.js.map